AYTAC GAHRAMANOVA

FRONT END DEVELOPER





+994557150540



aytac2003qehremanova@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/aytac-gahramanova-6b61ab245/



https://github.com/AytajGahramanova

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- SASS/SCSS
- Tailwind CSS
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- Node.js
- React
- MongoDB
- Next.is

EDUCATION

BAKU STATE UNIVERSITY

Computer Science

2020-2024

PROFILE

I am experienced in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and React, along with expertise in modern libraries and frameworks. Known for strong creative and analytical problem-solving skills, I pay meticulous attention to detail. A collaborative team player, I consistently contribute to the success and innovation of projects.

EXPERIENCE

FRONT END DEVELOPER

Kvadrat MMC 27/08/2024 - 27/11/2024

- Collaborating with the team on various stages of projects using React and Tailwind CSS.
- Expertise in creating efficient and high-performance web applications using Next.js.

FRONT END DEVELOPER

Khan Buta Group MMC

04/03/2024 - 04/08/2024

- Practices to improve the appearance of websites and solve errors.
- Updating the sites according to the customer's request.

FRONT END DEVELOPER

Proton MMC 30/06/2023 - 30/09/2023

- Built responsive and accessible websites using Bootstrap, CSS, SCSS/SASS resulting in improved user engagement and experience.
- Created interactive web components and animations using JavaScript, resulting in visually appealing designs.